joyofrunning.in 2009-11-10

# Airtel Delhi Half Marathon 2009

**Joyforrunning Privacy statement**

**Information About Our Organization and Website:** This Privacy Statement applies to [ **www.joyofrunning.in**](http://www.joyofrunning.in/).  [ **www.joyofrunning.in**](http://www.joyofrunning.in/) is owned and maintained by Animonlive New Delhi, on behalf of Bharti Airtel Ltd.  

**Personally Identifiable Information We Collect From You:** During a visit to our site, personally identifiable information may be collected through any means or data flow channels.  

**Sharing Your Information** : [**www.joyofrunning.in**](http://www.joyofrunning.in/)  does not sell, rent, share or otherwiseprovide any of your information to anyone other than for site analytics as described in this policy.

We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions or to provide specific services or information.

**_Legal Disclaimer_**  

Under no circumstances Bharti Airtel Limited or any of its affiliates, subsidiaries or group companies alongwith its officers or employees are responsible or liable, in whatsoever manner, for maintenance and operations of this website or any material provided thereon. 

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, such as responses to civil or criminal subpoenas, or other requests by law enforcement personnel. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding or other legal process or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
